Guide to the Papers of Peter Koch, 1974-2003 M1584
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series IV. JOB FILES, CHRONOLOGICAL
  - Job files, 1987
    - D. Gilhooly, "Grocery Bag Portfolio"; # 318 (Carton 9)
    - George Foz/ Gardiner Fulmer Lithograph B.C; #319 (Carton 9)
    - David Meckel BUSINESS CARDS; #320 (Carton 9)
    - Peter Coyote Stationery; #321 (Carton 9)
    - Eliot Holtzman Photography Brochure; #322 (Carton 9)
    - Wanderley Revert House Cleaning (Lonnie Graham Design); #323 (Carton 9)
    - "The Task of Medicine" Kerr L. White Kaiser Family Foundation; #679 (Carton 28)
  - Job files, 1988
    - Newpaper Articles Re: P. Koch; #831 (Carton 9)
    - Stirking Research Gold- California Private Academic Libraries Pamphlet (Carton 9)
    - Hotzman Christmas Card; #327 (Carton 9)
    - Mondavi Christmas Party Invitations and Eps.; #328 (Carton 9)
    - Robert and Margrit Biever Christmas Card (Mondavi); #329 (Carton 9)
    - Mondavi Christmas Card and EP; #330 (Carton 9)
    - Susannah Hayes BUSINESS CARDS, Stationery, EP; #331 (Carton 9)
    - Family Genealogy: Adolphius Andrews; #332 (Carton 9)
    - GLA Albert Shumate Announcements; #333 (Carton 9)
    - Roxburghe /Zamorano Joint Meeting Announcements; #334 (Carton 9)
    - Annual Meeting Announcements (John Law); #335 (Carton 9)
    - GLA Annual Meeting (John Law) Keepsake; #336 (Carton 9)
    - GLA Spring Tour Announcements (Rodin Gardens); #337 (Carton 9)
    - GLA Spring Meeting Program Borghes #338 (Carton 9)
    - GLA Christmas Greeting and Insert; #339 (Carton 9)
    - GLA Winter Meeting Announcement #341 (Carton 9)
    - James Prestini 80th Birthday Announcement; #342 (Carton 9)
    - Andrea Sohn Design Stationery and EP; #343 (Carton 9)
    - Meckel Birth Announcements and EP (M. Manwaring Design); #344 (Carton 9)
    - Bramalea Pacific Christmas Card; #345 (Carton 9)
    - Ex libris Marlene Clements; #346 (Carton 9)
    - McDonald/Connacher Wedding; #347 (Carton 9)
    - Style Francais/Limn-Roset Announcements; #348 (Carton 9)
    - Cobden-Sanderson Doves Coaster: Roz/Zam Keepsake; #349 (Carton 9)
    - Robert Mondavi Winery Symposium Invitation, RSVP and EP; #350 (Carton 9)
    - Stefonie Marlis Promotional Brochure and EP; #351 (Carton 9)
    - "Howard A Friedman 1919-1988" Memorial; #352 (Carton 9)
    - Roxburghe Club Announcements- Daid lane Goines; # 353 (Carton 9)
    - Roxburghe Club Keepsake- Emperor Norton and Hawaii, Paul Kahn; # 353 (Carton 9)
    - "Musicality" Barbara Guest- Kelsey Street Press Design; # 356 (Carton 9)
    - "Elegy for the Dusky Seaside Sparrow"-Broadside-Michael Rothenberg Distinguished Award: Fine Print; #357 (Carton 9)
    - "Man Woman" Joanne Kyger, Michael Rothenberg, Big Bridge Press; #358 (Carton 9)
    - Bioethics Institute Invitation (4pc.); # 359 (Carton 9)
    - Form and Beyond- USF Symposium Poster; # 360 (Carton 9)
    - The Taske of Medicine" Dialogue at Wickenberg- Kerr L. White- Kaiser Family Foundation; # 361 (Carton 9)
    - The Task of Medicine- Cover Reprint- Kaiser Family Booklet; # 362 (Carton 9)
  - Job files, 1989
    - "The Early Years of the Black Stone Press in S.F."- Article in Book Club Quarterly: Vol LIV, #2; # 832 (Carton 9)
    - Mondavi Business Cards--Various States; #363 (Carton 9)
    - House Cleaning Mixed Media Pamphlet, Business Cards and EP; #364 (Carton 9)
    - "Pathways to Health" Kaiser Book; #365 (Carton 9)
    - Eliot Holtzman Stationery and Self Promotion Booklet and EP; #367 (Carton 9)
    - Mondavi Business Cards- Various States; #369 (Carton 9)
    - Maurice Powers Bookplate; #370 (Carton 9)
    - Peter Coyote Stationery; #377 (Carton 9)
    - Sitwell Bookplate; #372 (Carton 9)
    - "Voyelles" Rimbaud- New College Press; #373 (Carton 9)
    - GLA Winter Meeting Announcements- Yosemite; #375 (Carton 10)
    - GLA Winter Meeting Keepsake- Yosemite; #376 (Carton 10)
    - Yosemite Greeting Card; #377 (Carton 10)
    - GLA Autumn Meeting Keepsake- Grapes of Wrath; # 378 (Carton 10)
    - GLA Meeting Announcements- Grapes of Wrath; #379 (Carton 10)
    - GLA Christmas Greeting- John de Pol; # 380 (Carton 10)
    - GLA Annual Meeting Keepsake- W.P. Barlow; #381 (Carton 10)
    - GLA Annual Meeting Announcement- W.P. Barlow; # 382 (Carton 10)
    - GLA Spring Tour; # 383 (Carton 10)
    - GLA EP; #384 (Carton 10)
    - Flying Pig Artwork; #385 (Carton 10)
    - "Slow Joy"- S. Marlis book- Typesetting and Cover Design; #386 (Carton 10)
    - GLA Eric Gill Exhibit Announcement; #387 (Carton 10)
    - Conference on the under representation if minorities in the Medical and other professions- Kaiser Family Booklet Reprint; #389 (Carton 10)
    - Kahn Birth Announcement; #391 (Carton 10)
    - Sharafian Stationery; #392 (Carton 10)
    - Fred Cody Award Citation Sonia Blackman; #393 (Carton 10)
    - Colophon Club ABCXYZ Announcement; #394 (Carton 10)
    - Prestini Invitation; #395 (Carton 10)
    - Corey Holiday Card; #397 (Carton 10)
    - "Cultural Landscapes" Selborne- Stanford University Book; #398 (Carton 10)
    - Gilhooly Document-2 Breakfast Pack, 2 coffee break; #399 (Carton 10)
    - James Snyder Business Cards; #400 (Carton 10)
    - Howard Friedman Memorial Booklet and EP; #401 (Carton 10)
    - Colophon Club 1979-1989 Menu; #402 (Carton 10)
    - Paul Mittelstadt Business Cards (L. Graham Design); #403 (Carton 10)
    - Jeffrey Davis Business Cards and Stationery (L. Graham Design); #404 (Carton 10)
  - Job files, 1990
    - "Book Extensions"- Book Arts Symposium at San Francisco State; #833 (Carton 10)
    - Lecture to Friends of Paul Leonard Library; #834 (Carton 10)
    - "Favorite Songs" Michael Rothenberg- Big Bridge Press; #406 (Carton 10)
    - Mondavi Christmas Card; #407 (Carton 10)
    - Marlis Pullman Business Card; #408 (Carton 10)
    - Eliot Holtzman Photography: Business Cards, Pricelists, stationery and EP; #409 (Carton 10)
    - "The Bromeliads" Bookplate; #410 (Carton 10)
    - Andrea Sohn Design Business Cards; #411 (Carton 10)
    - Doug Johns Wedding Announcements; #412 (Carton 10)
    - GLA Christmas Card; #413 (Carton 10)
    - Eric Gill Keepsake-Rox/Zamorano; #414 (Carton 10)
    - GLA Annual Meeting Announcement- Kenneth Hill; #415 (Carton 10)
    - GLA Spring Tour Announcements-Libraries; #416 (Carton 10)
    - USF Summer Symposium "Midsummer Madness" Poster; #417 (Carton 10)
    - GLA Annual Meeting Keepsake- Kenneth Hill; #418 (Carton 10)
    - "Round Midnight" Adam Comford Altazor Ed (New College); #419 (Carton 10)
    - William Danner Birth Announcement; #421 (Carton 10)
    - Sharafian Wedding Announcement; #422 (Carton 10)
    - Smith and Hawken Posters; #423 (Carton 10)
    - "Hanging Fire" Portfolio- Barbara Foster: 8 pc. Text and document; #424 (Carton 10)
    - "The Task of Medicine"- Kaiser brochure (3rd printing); #425 (Carton 10)
    - "Looking fo Kafka" Stanford University Pamphlet: John Felstiner, Department of English; #426 (Carton 10)
    - Stephanie Marlis Card; #427 (Carton 10)
    - Bancroft Library Annual Exhibition Announcement; #428 (Carton 10)
    - Gregynog Press Announcement- Book Club of CA; #429 (Carton 10)
    - Tuscany Alley Announcement; #430 (Carton 10)
    - Diane Wakoski Announcement- Book Club of CA; #431 (Carton 10)
    - G.L. Donohue Rare Book Room Announcement- W.P. Wreden; #434 (Carton 10)
    - Robert Werner Business Cards; #435 (Carton 10)
    - Natkin Weisbach Higginbotham- "What Is a Boy?"; #436 (Carton 10)
    - Danner Christmas Card; #437 (Carton 10)
    - Roe Birth Announcement; #438 (Carton 10)
    - Walker Avenue Stationery (David Roe); #439 (Carton 10)
    - Thomas Goldwasser Rare Books; #440 (Carton 10)
    - "Book for Sensei" Poems M. McClure, P. Whalen, J. Kuggen, M. Rothenberg, J. Harrison, A. Codrescue- Big Bridge Press; #441 (Carton 10)
    - Masako Wedding; #442 (Carton 10)
    - "The Bromeliads"- Leon Duval; #443 (Carton 10)
    - "The Bromeliads"; Leon Duval - Big Bridge Press; #444 (Carton 10)
    - Mimi Nielson B.C. and Cert.; #445 (Carton 10)
    - Peter Koch Business Cards; #446 (Carton 10)
    - Miles Karpilow Stat (2 letter head, ep); #447 (Carton 10)
    - Koch Annual Party Invitations; #448 (Carton 10)
    - New College Book Arts Brochure; #449 (Carton 10)
  - Job files, 1991
    - Armory Center Show; #835 (Carton 10)
    - Consortium of Book Arts Educators; #836 (Carton 10)
    - National Book Arts Conference Sponsored By New College Book Arts Program; #837 (Carton 10)
    - Printed Ephemera Announcing Peter Kochs Shows/Lectures; #838 (Carton 10)
    - New York Public Library Loans, Openings, Packing List #819 (Carton 10)
    - Yellowstone Art Center- University of Montana- Lecture/Missoula Dept. of Art/Bize/Helena; #824 (Carton 10)
    - Lament O the Laundromat- Greg Keeler Broadside; #452 (Carton 10)
    - The Coyotes Annc.; #452 (Carton 11)
    - Burton Weiss Business Cards, Bookselle Annc. and Stat. (4pc.); #454 (Carton 11)
    - The Book Club of CA Quarterly NL Vol. LIX Bid; #445 (Carton 11)
    - Friends of the Bancroft Library Exhibit Annc.; #456 (Carton 11)
    - Barbara Galuszka Parsons Business Cards; #457 (Carton 11)
    - Powis Parker Business Cards (imprint name only); #458 (Carton 11)
    - SFAI Store- Gail Ganino Business Cards; #459 (Carton 11)
    - Ex libris "In Memory of D. Steven Corey Book Plate; #460 (Carton 11)
    - GLA Annual Meeting Keepsake- Maps; #461 (Carton 11)
    - Italy: Educator of Europe Annc. - USF and Poster; #462 (Carton 11)
    - Donohue Rare Book Room Adrian Wilson USF Collection Annc.; #463 (Carton 11)
    - Symposium Schedule - USF, Italy: Educator of Europe; #464 (Carton 11)
    - 'Little Canto' - Tom Clark, New College Chapbook #465 (Carton 11)
    - Autumn Meeting Keepsake - St. Jerome/Icon of Book; #466 (Carton 11)
    - GLA Autumn Meeting Annc.; #467 (Carton 11)
    - GLA Xmas Card; #468 (Carton 11)
    - USF Citations: Paul Birkel and S.J. Dullea; #469 (Carton 11)
    - GLA Winter Meeting Keepsake - Gutenberg and The Cyclotron; #470 (Carton 11)
    - GLA Alfred Kennedy Memorial Annc.; #472 (Carton 11)
    - 'Alphabet Book' - Philip Kuzinicki; #473 (Carton 11)
    - Alaphabet Book Annc. Request for Payment; #474 (Carton 11)
    - Peter Koch New Years Card; #475 (Carton 11)
    - Adam Joseph Meckel Birth Annc.; #477 (Carton 11)
    - Moises Book Stall Annc.; #478 (Carton 11)
    - Califia Books Barbara Parsons Annc.; #480 (Carton 11)
    - Book Club of CA Annc.m #481 (Carton 11)
    - Paula Marie Gourley - Business Cards; #482 (Carton 11)
    - Kenter Canyon Stat. and EP/ Letterhead; #483 (Carton 11)
    - Memory Skates Holiday Card - S. Marlis/ Driscoll Design Xmas Card/Steward; #484 (Carton 11)
    - Phyllis Friedman Stationary and EP; #485 (Carton 11)
    - Roxbughe Club Dinner Checks; #486 (Carton 11)
    - Roxbughe Club Dinner Check and Certificate of Appreciation; #487 (Carton 11)
  - Job files, 1992
    - Roxburghe Keepsake Book; #1397 (Carton 11)
    - GLA Winter Meeting Keepsake - W. Fargo; #488 (Carton 11)
    - GLA Winter Meeting Announcement - Wells Fargo; #489 (Carton 11)
    - Donald Reardon Bookplate USF; #490 (Carton 11)
    - GLA Annual Meeting Announcement; #491 (Carton 11)
    - GLA Annual Meeting Keepsake; #492 (Carton 11)
    - GLA Envelopes; #494 (Carton 11)
    - Susan Snyder Notecard; #495 (Carton 11)
    - Rare Book Catalog Awards P. Koch Presenter; #840 (Carton 11)
    - Claremont College Show; #839 (Carton 11)
    - USF Presidents Xmas Card; #496 (Carton 11)
    - GLA Summer Symposium Announcement; #497 (Carton 11)
    - Friends of the Bancroft Library Exhibit Announcement; #498 (Carton 11)
    - USF Statement of Mission; #499 (Carton 11)
    - Glenn Snyder Business Cards; #500 (Carton 11)
    - Barbara Parsons Relocation; #501 (Carton 11)
    - Sylvia Solocheck Walters; #502 (Carton 11)
    - GLA Fall Meeting Keepsake - R. Rodriguez; #503 (Carton 11)
    - GLA Fall Meeting Announcement - "My Disc. of CA"; #504 (Carton 11)
    - GLA Spring Tour Announcement - Museum Afternoon; #506 (Carton 11)
    - 'A Sea Journey' Laurence Ferlinghetti, Bancroft Library Press/ Pressroom Ferlinghetti Project; #507 (Carton 11)
    - Business Card Design Peter Koch Printers; #508 (Carton 11)
    - Dorothy McGilvry Note paper, cards, EP; #510 (Carton 11)
    - Amy Nathan Promo. - 2 cards, EP; #512 (Carton 11)
    - 'Him Her, Them' Hap Klop - (Paul Tsang Design) Poems; #513 (Carton 11)
    - Weber/Greenberg Wedding Invitation: 4pc. Announcement, RSVP, 2 ep.; #514 (Carton 11)
    - Snyder/Jones Wedding Announcement; #515 (Carton 11)
    - Library Relations/Ratinoff/Anais Nin Announcement and EPl #516 (Carton 11)
    - Jennings/Hulburd Wedding Card and EP; #518 (Carton 11)
    - B. Parson Exhibit Announcement Rosicrucian Museum; #520 (Carton 11)
    - The Book Club of CA - Business Cards; #521 (Carton 11)
    - Roxburghe Club/ Charles Fracchia Announcement; #522 (Carton 11)
    - P. Koch New Years Card/Xmas; #523 (Carton 11)
    - Friends of the Bancroft Library - "Gifts to the Library" Exhibit Announcement/ Bancroft Card; #524 (Carton 11)
    - Peter Coyote Stat.; #525 (Carton 11)
    - The Garden - Paul Piper Broadside/ Missoula; #526 (Carton 11)
  - Job files, 1993
    - Schlegal Christmas Card and EP/ USF Presidents Xmas; #630 (Carton 11)
    - P. Koch Nomination for "Oscar Lewis Award" (Book Club of CA); #841 (Carton 11)
    - Burton Weiss Stat. and eps; #528 (Carton 11)
    - Jonathan Hammer T. Page - Trestlework; #529 (Carton 11)
    - Celeste Lilienthal Roe Birth Announcement/David Roe; #530 (Carton 11)
    - GL Bookplate (w/mice); #533 (Carton 12)
    - Book Club of California - B. Middleton Lecture Announcement; #534 (Carton 12)
    - Book Club of California/GLA Lecture - Kim Merker Announcement; #535 (Carton 12)
    - Bancroft Library 46th Ann. Meeting Invit. and Ep; #539 (Carton 12)
    - Goldwasser Cover; #540 (Carton 12)
    - Colophon/Roxburghe joint Meeting AnnouncementBringhurst; #541 (Carton 12)
    - Book Club of California Announcement - L.C. Powell; #542 (Carton 12)
    - Silckerodt (sp?)/ Lippold Wedding Announcement and eps; #544 (Carton 12)
    - USF Darwin Symposium Prog.; #545 (Carton 12)
    - Steve Sharafian Stat.; #548 (Carton 12)
    - Counting the house - Richard Gordon Photo Book (5 pc, letterpress pgs only); #549 (Carton 12)
    - P. Koch Party Invit.; #550 (Carton 12)
    - California Society of Printmakers - Beth van Hoesen Cert.; #551 (Carton 12)
    - GLA Winter Meeting Keepsake; #552 (Carton 12)
    - GLA Membership Fund Card; #553 (Carton 12)
    - GLA Winter Meeting Announcement; #554 (Carton 12)
    - GLA Xmas Card and Ep; #555 (Carton 12)
    - USF Darwin Symposium Program; #556 (Carton 12)
    - GLA Annual Meeting Keepsake; #557 (Carton 12)
    - GLA Annual Meeting Announcement; #558 (Carton 12)
    - GLA Fall Meeting Keepsake; #559 (Carton 12)
    - GLA Fall Meeting Announcement; #560 (Carton 12)
    - Friends of the Bancroft Library; #1362 (Carton 12)
  - Job files, 1994 (Carton 12)
    - Preparations for New York Public Library / San Francisco Public Library Show; #805 (Carton 12)
    - Drafts of New York Public Library / San Francisco Public Library Catalogs; #806 (Carton 12)
    - New York Public Library / San Francisco Public Library Catalog Layout; #807 (Carton 12)
    - Receipts for Making Catalog; #808 (Carton 12)
    - Correspondence RE: catalog and drafts of included essays; #809 (Carton 12)
    - "Artists Statement" - P. Koch for New York Public Library / San Francisco Public Library Show; #810 (Carton 12)
    - Mailing List New York Public Library / San Francisco Public Library Show; #811 (Carton 12)
    - Final Accounting New York Public Library / San Francisco Public Library Catalog; #812 (Carton 12)
    - Checklists of Catalog Materials; #813
    - New York Public Library / San Francisco Public Library Show Announcement and Poster; #814 (Carton 12)
    - Proposal for SFPL - RE: Printing Catalog; #815 (Carton 12)
    - NYPL Press Releases; #820 (Carton 12)
    - Press Release by Stephanie Marlis; #821 (Carton 12)
    - Retrospective Catalog; #822 (Carton 12)
    - Lisa Browar Intro for NYPL Poster; #823 (Carton 12)
    - San Francisco Public Library Exhibition Preparations; #825 (Carton 12)
    - "Peter R. Koch, Printer" Article in GLA Newsletter; #842 (Carton 12)
    - SF MOMA Rentral Gallery Show; #843 (Carton 12)
    - SFPL Loan Agreement; #844 (Carton 12)
    - Thomas A. Goldwasser Ad Design; #570 (Carton 12)
    - Thomas A. Goldwasser Rare Books Catalog 6; #571 (Carton 12)
    - "The Blind Horses" - Ed Lahey; #562 (Carton 12)
    - P. Koch, Printer (NYPL Book Cover); #563 (Carton 12)
    - P. Koch, Printer (New York Public Library Show Announcement); #564 (Carton 12)
    - The Book Club of California - Pacific Book Auction; #565 (Carton 12)
    - Mark Other Place - Philip Whalen (Big Bridge Press) - Job Canceled; #566 (Carton 12)
    - The Quarterly Newsletter Vol LIX No. 3; #567 (Carton 12)
    - The Book Club of California Quarterly N.L. Vol. LIX No. 4; #568 (Carton 12)
    - The Book Club of California Quarterly NL Vol. LIX No. 2; #569 (Carton 12)
    - GL David Oyler Thank you Card; #572 (Carton 12)
    - Grolier Club Announcement (Not Printed); #573 (Carton 12)
    - S.F. State Urban Instit. Logo Design (Not Used); #574 (Carton 12)
    - Hormone Derange Ed. Travelling Card (2 states); #575 (Carton 12)
    - "A Peck of Gold" Broadside - GAITE; #576 (Carton 12)
    - Ann Whipple B-Day Announcement and Ep; #577 (Carton 12)
    - Towell-Karel Wedding Invit. and Ep; #578 (Carton 12)
    - GL - David K Oyler Bookmark; #579 (Carton 12)
    - Ann Fields - The Collected Poems, Big Bridge Press, Cover; #580 (Carton 12)
    - "Alanas Blessing" - Maryanna Shaw, Stockholm; #581 (Carton 12)
    - Maryanna and Charles Stockholm; #582 (Carton 12)
    - Laurie Thompson B.C.; #583 (Carton 12)
    - The Friends of the Bancroft Lib. Annual Meeting Program and Ep; #584 (Carton 12)
    - The Friends of the Bancroft Lib. Postcard; #585 (Carton 12)
    - GLA USF Bookplates-Curotto Endowment in memory of Duggan Fam.; #586 (Carton 12)
    - "Deep Food Defictions" Party Invitation; #587 (Carton 12)
    - Susannah Hays B.C.; Stat. and EP; #588 (Carton 12)
    - P. Koch, Printer - Invitation to Roxborghe Club, Lecture and EP; #589 (Carton 12)
    - Ruth Bernhard Portfolio - Tenazas Designs 13 pc.; #590 (Carton 12)
    - Peter Koch, Printer, Catalog; #592 (Carton 12)
    - Elers Koch/Bancroft Library Book class; #591 (Carton 13)
    - Book Club Postcards; #593 (Carton 13)
    - GLA Annual Meeting Announcement; #594 (Carton 13)
    - GLA Annual Meeting; #595 (Carton 13)
    - Gleeson Library Associates (GLA) winter meeting announcement and keepsake; #596 (Carton 13)
    - Gleeson Library Associates; #597 (Carton 13)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Xmas card and EP; #598 (Carton 13)
    - Gleeson Library Associates fall meeting keepsake; #599 (Carton 13)
    - Gleeson Library, fall 1994; #600 (Carton 13)
    - Gleeson Library Associates letterhead and EPS; #601 (Carton 13)
    - Gleeson Library Associates; #1242 (Carton 13)
    - New York Public Library / San Francisco Public Library Catalog Cover; #804 (Carton 12)
    - Gerbode Foundation; #? (Carton 12)
  - Job files, 1995
    - Gleeson Library Associates remit Ep; #1355
    - The Friends of the Bancroft Statement and Cards; #1365 (Carton 13)
    - Friends of the Bancroft Ackn. Card; #1364 (Carton 13)
    - Bancroft Library/Final Proofs for repro.; #1363 (Carton 13)
    - The Bancroft Library Stationery; #1369 (Carton 13)
    - Thomas Goldwasser; #unknown (Carton 13)
    - Bancroft Library Annual Gifts card; #unknown (Carton 13)
    - Holtzman Brochure; #unknown (Carton 13)
    - Anninger/Harvard; #816 (Carton 13)
    - Loan: New York Public Library Exhibit; #817 (Carton 13)
    - New York Public Library Show Agenda; #818 (Carton 13)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Insert/Program; #602 (Carton 13)
    - Gleeson Library Associates winter Meeting Announcement; #603 (Carton 13)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Keepsake winter; #604 (Carton 13)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Annual Meeting Announcement; #605 (Carton 13)
    - Roxborghe Club, September; #606 (Carton 13)
    - Peter Koch Party, September; #607 (Carton 13)
    - Irving W. Robbins; #608 (Carton 13)
    - Book Club of California - Ballooning - J. Pevsner Announcement; #609 (Carton 13)
    - Dave Thomas, Mexico Museum Poems; #610 (Carton 13)
    - Harvard Catalog Output; #611 (Carton 13)
    - Book Club of California - Charles Mould; #612 (Carton 13)
    - Hall/Butler Xmas Party Invites; #613 (Carton 13)
    - Book Club of California - Ballooning exhibition Announcement; #614 (Carton 13)
    - Vision Editions; #615 (Carton 13)
    - John Windle Antiquarian Bookseller "Open"; #616 (Carton 13)
    - John Windle Antiquarian Bookseller sign; #617 (Carton 13)
    - Video Plus B.C. (job cancelled); #618 (Carton 13)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Fall Meeting Announcement; #619 (Carton 13)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Xmas Card and EP; #620 (Carton 13)
    - Gleeson Library Associates O. Wilde Keepsake Broadside; #621 (Carton 13)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Fall Meeting Keepsake; #622 (Carton 13)
    - Connor Flanagan Birth Announcement and EP; #623 (Carton 13)
    - "Follow the Parade" - Tsang Design Card; #625 (Carton 13)
    - Spaulding/Dodd Wedding Poem Broadside; #626 (Carton 13)
    - Book Club of California - Jacqueline Kazarian Annc; #627 (Carton 13)
    - Brayman Wedding Invite, RSVP card, and EP; #628 (Carton 13)
    - Yao-Fen You Commencement Announcement; #629 (Carton 13)
    - Thomas A. Goldwasser Rare Books Catalogue 10 cover; #630 (Carton 13)
    - Wm. Stout Xmas Card; #631 (Carton 13)
    - SF MOMA Library bookplate; #632 (Carton 13)
    - Galway Kinnell Poem (Holtzman Keepsake); #633 (Carton 13)
    - Susannah Hayes Moving Announcement; #634 (Carton 13)
    - Burton Weiss Stat and EP; #635 (Carton 13)
    - Beatrice Bowles B.C.; #636 (Carton 13)
    - Eliot Holtzman Photography Labels; #637 (Carton 13)
    - Peter Koch, Printer, Harvard University Exhibition Annoucement, #638 (Carton 13)
    - H. Derange Broadside, "Proscenium" - John Yau, #639 (Carton 13)
    - H. Derange Broadside, "That Old Gang of Mind" - Milo Miles; #640 (Carton 13)
    - Friends of Fr. Monahan; #1201 (Carton 13)
    - Bancroft Library; #1212 (Carton 13)
  - Job files, 1996
    - Shirafian Stationery; #1360 (Carton 14)
    - Friends of Bancroft Library Repro-proofs and Stationery; #1358 (Carton 14)
    - Bancroft Friends Council Stationery; #1354 (Carton 14)
    - USF Reply EP; #1371 (Carton 14)
    - Joseph Goldyne/stationery; #1368 (Carton 14)
    - Bancroft Library Stationery; #1367 (Carton 14)
    - Stockholm; #1378 (Carton 14)
    - Charles M. Stockholm; #1379 (Carton 14)
    - Bancroft Stationery/ Council Fall 96; #1366 (Carton 14)
    - Nina Wemyss bus. Card; #unknown (Carton 14)
    - San Francisco Public Library collection; #845 (Carton 14)
    - UCLA/UC joint certificate; #1380 (Carton 14)
    - Pacific Book Auction Gallery; #unknown (Carton 14)
    - Book Club Post Card; #unknown (Carton 14)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Winter Meeting; # unknown (Carton 14)
    - Mary Williams/Matlack; #unknown (Carton 14)
    - 17th Street Studios; #unknown (Carton 14)
    - Koch Party Coasters; #unknown (Carton 14)
    - G.B. Carson; #unknown (Carton 14)
    - Sean Thackery; #unknown (Carton 14)
    - Sean Thackery Coaster; #unknown (Carton 14)
    - Mimi Nielsen/Nelson Construction; #unknown (Carton 14)
    - Thomas Sanchez Bus. Card; #unknown (Carton 14)
    - PBAG Cards; #unknown (Carton 14)
    - Gleeson Library Associates annual Meeting; #unknown (Carton 14)
    - Tsang Cmment (Miriam Mackarness Bus. Card); #unknown (Carton 14)
    - Stefanie Marlis; #unknown (Carton 14)
    - John Windle/Bookplates; #unknown (Carton 14)